llewellyn.com 2010-12-29

# Llewellyn Worldwide - About Us: Privacy Policy

Effective 9/1/ 2009

**Table of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any Llewellyn World website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are as follows: 

> **Consumer Orders;**  
>  Name   
>  Address   
>  Email address   
>  Phone number   
>  Credit/Debit Card Information   
>  Date of Birth (Optional) 

> **Business Orders;**  
>  Business Name  
>  Address  
>  Phone  
>  Fax  
>  Business Type  
>  Job Title 

> **Astrology Reports;**  
>  Full name   
>  Date of Birth  
>  Birth City   
>  Birth State   
>  Birth County  
>  Birth Country  
>  Current Address - City, State, County, Country 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order an astrology report or a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

> **Gifts sent directly to a third party;**   
>  Name   
>  Address 

> **Astrology Reports on a third party;**  
>  Full name   
>  Date of Birth  
>  Birth City   
>  Birth State   
>  Birth County  
>  Birth Country  
>  Current Address - City, State, County, Country 

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses may be used to provide you with promotional and company information. These addresses are not shared with outside parties.

All users that register with our website will receive our product catalog; you can also register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. You can opt out of receiving our updates at any time by completing the form on our unsubscribe page at http://www.llewellyn.com/newsletters.php

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to be used by our sales and marketing departments. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by sending your request to;

> Web Master  
>  Llewellyn Worldwide, LTD.  
>  2143 Wooddale Drive  
>  Woodbury, MN 55125  
> 

Please include your full name, current address, and a daytime phone number. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by logging into your account on our website and updating the information or by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How to Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-THE MOON or visit the contact us page of our website at http://www.llewellyn.com/about/contact_us.php.
